leethax.net 2016-02-19

# Privacy Policy - leethax.net

| 

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, leethax.net collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. leethax.net’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how leethax.net’s visitors use its website. From time to time, leethax.net may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

leethax.net also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for users engaging in interactions on the website, such as leaving comments or participating in the website poll. leethax.net does not disclose such information to third parties, except as explained below. 

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to leethax.net choose to interact with leethax.net in ways that require leethax.net to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that leethax.net gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, visitors may optionally enter an e-mail address when leaving comments. Visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

### Aggregated Statistics

leethax.net may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, leethax.net may monitor the most popular pages on the website. leethax.net may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, leethax.net does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

leethax.net will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. leethax.net discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when leethax.net believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of leethax.net, third parties or the public at large. If you have supplied your e-mail address to leethax.net, leethax.net may occasionally send you an email to contact you regarding the context where you entered your e-mail address, such as notifications of new features or to solicit your feedback. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. leethax.net takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. leethax.net uses cookies to help leethax.net identify and track visitors, their usage of leethax.net website, and their website access preferences. leethax.net visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using leethax.net, with the drawback that certain features of leethax.net may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

### Ads

Ads appearing on leethax.net may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by leethax.net and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, leethax.net may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in leethax.net’s sole discretion. leethax.net encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

|
